Shorena K. Anzhilov Full Stack Software Engineer Miami Beach, Florida + 1 (786) 244-7378

shorenaanzhilov@gmail.com II https://github.com/ShorenaK II https://www.linkedin.com/in/shorenaanzhilov/

I am a team-oriented well-rounded, non-traditional full-stack software developer who believes in using clean, maintainable code to create ethical, accessible software products. With 10 years experience in business operation and management I bring to the table a passion for making communications accessible, and cultivating exceptional teams that focus on creative problem-solving, with an eye toward the bigger picture.

SKILLS:

Languages - JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Python, SQL, Mongo, JSON, Typerscript, EJS

Libraries and Frameworks - React, Bootstrap, Express.js, Django, Jquery.

Database - MongoDB, PostgreSQL.

Other Software Systems - API's, Mongoose, Command Line Interface, Software version control (Git/Github), VSCode, Heroku, Slack, Trello.

Other - Spoken Languages English(Fluent), Russian(Fluent) and Georgian(Fluent).

PROJECTS:

Web Application "Profolios" - Django , Python, PostgreSQL.

09/2022

Technologies used:

Django, Python, PostgreSQL.

Online directory for exposure of all users portfolios! ability to create and share portfolios with projects, Web App also has user's Registration and Authentication functions.

Web Application "MyBooksy" - a Full-Stack MERN application.

09/2022

Technologies used:

The application was built with React, MongoDB, Express, Node, CSS.

"MyBooksy" is Full- Stack MERN application, users a book enthusiasts can find their next read.

User also can post own book and add affiliate link for extra exposure with MyBooksy platform.

Web app also allows the user to post reviews, add likes and recommendations.

Web Application "KIBI" a full stack, e-commerce, web application that features the 7 RESTful routes. 08/2022

Technologies used:

The application was built with Node.js, Mongoose, Express and EJS. The file structure is compliant with the MVC & MVP formats.

There are two different models, each with corresponding seed files. Some of the HTML is set up using EJS Partials. The repository is maintained on Github.

The application is deployed on Heroku.

Web Application II ("Black Jack" web application to play Black Jack game.)

08/2022

Technologies used:

The application was built with HTML, CSS, JavaScript.

Html was use to create containers of for the card elements, buttons . Css styled the front and backgrounds of containers & Html pages.

JavaScript is used for functionality, logic and DOM manipulation.

User of the fully functional "Black Jack" web app can play the game against the dealer.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

NS Global Commerce LLC, Brooklyn, New York Founder/CEO

08/2017 - 12/2021

- Implemented new consumer service management tools, decreasing order handling time by 50%.
- Managed website overhaul and rebrand, including the addition of e-commerce
- Joined hands with reputable manufacturers and suppliers to import great quality products.
- Built customer loyalty through customer service excellence.
- Developed highly skilled, motivated, inspired and committed employees.
- Handling a complex business operation & strategic planning.
- Grew digital outreach with a 20 % increase in revenue .

Sishodia Law, P.C. New York, New York

01/2016 - 08/2017

Paralegal

- Coordinated Real Estate Law Firm operations to serve 100 + clients.
- Maintaining detail-oriented database records to ensure timely and appropriate care given to all clients.
- · Handled quick-book entry for accurate accounting collaborated with the office manager to standardize billing practices that contributed to a 15 % increase in profitability.
- Achieved in-demand status amongst paralegal colleagues, often personally requested by senior partners to manage complex, deadline-intensive matters.

EDUCATION:

Software Engineering Immersive I General Assembly I San Francisco

07/2022-09/2022

Full-stack software development immersive student in an intensive, twelve-week, 420+ in-class hour program focused on product development fundamentals, object-oriented programming, MVC framework, data modeling, and team collaboration and communication strategies. Demonstrated technical proficiency through development of increasingly more advanced web applications.

BA, Science in Chemistry Biology

Ivane Javakhishvili State University II Tbilisi, Georgia